<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE Rules SYSTEM "../rules.dtd">

    <Unit id="thrower_4" category="unitcategory_artillery">
      <Name>Spear Thrower</Name>
      <Name lang="de_DE"> Speerschleuderer </Name>
      <Description lang="de_DE">
        <p>Ein Speer ist auch im Nahkampf, vor allem gegen Reiter, effektiv. Dumm nur, wenn man schon alle Speere weggeworfen hat, bevor ein Reiter angreift. Im Leitfaden für Speerwerfer steht, dass man immer einen Speer weniger werfen sollte, als man hat. Leider kann kein Speerwerfer zählen, geschweige denn lesen.</p> 
      </Description>
      <Description lang="en_US">
        <p>A spear is also effective at close range – especially against riders. The only problem is if you’ve thrown all your spears already before you’re attacked by a rider. The field manual for spear throwers clearly states: “Always throw one spear less than you have”. The trouble is, spear throwers can’t read, let alone count.</p>
      </Description>
      <Flavour lang="en_US">
        <p>Why anyone would bother to tie a stick to a stone is a mystery – stones are brilliant missiles. But the effect is fantastic, longer range, more accurate and easier to collect. What more could you want?</p>
      </Flavour>
      <Flavour lang="de_DE">
        <p>Wieso jemand einen Stock an einen Stein gebunden hat, ist unverständlich, denn Steine sind doch schon hervorragende Wurfgeschosse. Aber der Effekt ist großartig, größere Reichweite, zielgenauer und einfacher einzusammeln. Was will man mehr?</p>
      </Flavour>
      <Cost id="resource_stone" round="true">180</Cost>  
      <Cost id="resource_wood" round="true">180</Cost>
      <Cost id="resource_fur" round="true">280</Cost>    
      <ProductionTime shortenable="true">1300</ProductionTime>  
      <Velocity>1</Velocity>
      <ActionPoints>4</ActionPoints>
      <Initiative>8</Initiative>
      <Attack>12</Attack>
      <CriticalDamage chance="0.1">8</CriticalDamage>
      <Armor>3</Armor>
      <Overrunnable>true</Overrunnable>
      <Hitpoints>50</Hitpoints>
      <Effectiveness category="unitcategory_infantry">1.5</Effectiveness>
      <Effectiveness category="unitcategory_cavalry">0.75</Effectiveness>
      <Effectiveness category="unitcategory_artillery">0.75</Effectiveness>
      <Effectiveness category="unitcategory_siege">0.8</Effectiveness>  
      <Effectiveness category="unitcategory_special">1</Effectiveness>   
      <RequirementGroup>
        <Requirement id="building_firing_range" min_level="20" />
        <Requirement id="building_copper_smelter" min_level="1" />
      </RequirementGroup>
    </Unit>
