<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE Rules SYSTEM "../rules.dtd">

<Building id="building_fortress_fortification" group="military" category="building_category_fortress_fortification" buyable="true" destructable="false" demolishable="false">  
  <Name lang="de_DE">Festungsanlagen</Name>
  <Name lang="en_US">Fortifications</Name>
  <Description lang="de_DE">
    <p>Ein paar aufgetürmte Steinbrocken, zusammengebundene Baumstämme, ein provisorisches Tor. Fertig ist die Festung. Die Festungsanlagen bestehen aus einen Hauptgebäude, einem kleinen Versammlungsplatz und Mauern zur Verteidigung.</p>
    <p>In der Sicherheit der Festung bauen die Arbeiter schneller und Krieger werden schneller ausgebildet.</p>
    <p>Je größer die Festung wird, desto besser sind auch die Verteidigungsanlagen und Unterkünfte.</p>
  </Description>
  <Description lang="en_US">
    <p>Some debris, tied tree trunks, a provisional gate, small parade-ground, main building and some walls; rudimentary stronghold finished. Improving the fortification results in a higher maximum size of the garrison, speeding-up all other construction sites and increases the defensive abilities.</p> 
  </Description>
    <Flavour lang="en_US">
    <p>The fortification is controlling the region. Therefore armed forces are deployed to collect empathically the taxes and in case of attacks to protect the fortress. Prepare for battle!</p>
  </Flavour>
    <Flavour lang="de_DE">
    <p>Die Festung beherrscht die Region. Dafür werden Truppen aufgestellt, die die Steuern der Siedlungen eintreiben und die Festung vor Angriffen beschützen.</p>
  </Flavour>  
  <Cost id="resource_stone" round="true">FLOOR(30*POW(LEVEL,2.95)*(10*POW(LEVEL,-0.7))+0.5)</Cost>  
  <Cost id="resource_wood" round="true">FLOOR(30*POW(LEVEL,2.95)*(10*POW(LEVEL,-0.7))+0.5)</Cost>    
  <Cost id="resource_fur" round="true">FLOOR(((MIN(LEVEL,3)-MIN(LEVEL,2))*30*POW(LEVEL,2.95))*0.5*(10*POW(LEVEL,-0.7))+0.5)</Cost>
  <ProductionTime shortenable="false">FLOOR(((MIN(LEVEL+1,4)-MIN(LEVEL,4))*(293.33*POW(LEVEL,3)-1760*POW(LEVEL,2)+3286.7*LEVEL-1760)+(MIN(LEVEL,4)-MIN(LEVEL,3))*(6*POW(LEVEL,4.3)+250*LEVEL))*(10*POW(LEVEL,-0.7))+0.5)</ProductionTime>     
  <Abilities> <!-- just for grouping -->
    <UnlockGarrison level="1" />
    <GarrisonSizeBonus>1000</GarrisonSizeBonus>
    <ArmySizeBonus>1000</ArmySizeBonus>
    <CommandPoints>1</CommandPoints><!-- one for level 1, +1 for level 5, +1 for level 10-->
    <UnlockQueue  queue="queue_buildings" />
    <SpeedupQueue queue="queue_buildings" domain="settlement">2*FLOOR(1.88*POW(LEVEL,1.425)+0.5)/100.0</SpeedupQueue>
    <DefenseBonus>0.5*LEVEL</DefenseBonus>
  </Abilities>
</Building>