<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE Rules SYSTEM "rules.dtd">

<ResourceTypes>
  <Resource id="resource_stone" stealable="false">  
    <Name lang="de_DE">Stein</Name>
    <Name lang="en_US">Stone</Name>
    <Flavour lang="de_DE">Grau, hart, überall zu finden.</Flavour>
    <Flavour lang="en_US">Gray, hard, found everywhere.</Flavour>
    <Description lang="de_DE">
      <p>Steine -- in der STEINzeit DER Rohstoff schlechthin. Kann gesammelt, gestapelt, geschärft und geworfen werden. Mehr muss man nicht sagen.</p>
    </Description>
    <Description lang="en_US">
      <p>Ah, stones. The most vital raw material of the Stone Age. Can't think why they called it that... Stones can be gathered, stacked, sharpened and thrown. Not a lot more to say about them.</p>
    </Description>
  </Resource>
  <Resource id="resource_wood" stealable="false">  
    <Name lang="de_DE">Holz</Name>
    <Name lang="en_US">Wood</Name>
    <Flavour lang="de_DE">Ein Brett in Ehren kann niemand verwehren.</Flavour>
    <Flavour lang="en_US">It's not for nothing that we say 'touch wood' when we hope for good luck!</Flavour>
    <Description lang="de_DE">
      <p>Holz war bereits in der Steinzeit in allen Varianten verfügbar: Nadelholz, Laubholz, Kantholz und natürlich Brettholz. Als Rohstoff spielt Holz eine wichtige Rolle bei der Konstruktion von Gebäuden und Belagerungswaffen.</p>
    </Description>
    <Description lang="en_US">
      <p>Even in the Stone Age, wood was used for various important purposes, including the construction of buildings and siege weapons.</p>
    </Description>
  </Resource>
  <Resource id="resource_fur" stealable="false">
    <Name lang="de_DE">Fell</Name>
    <Name lang="en_US">Fur</Name>
    <Flavour lang="de_DE">In der gesamten Steinzeit wurden Kunstfelle verwendet, es kamen keine Tiere zu schaden. Natürlich!</Flavour>
    <Flavour lang="en_US">Naturally, throughout the entire stone age they only used artificial fur – so no animals were harmed, of course!  </Flavour>
    <Description lang="de_DE">
      <p>Hält warm, hält Wasser ab, verhängt Löcher und taugt im Notfall auch als rudimentäre Dachbedeckung.</p>
    </Description>
    <Description lang="en_US">
      <p>Fur, sweet fur. It keeps you warm, it's water resistant, it can cover up holes in buildings, and it can be used as emergency roofing.</p>
    </Description>
  </Resource>
  <Resource id="resource_cash" stealable="false" ratingValue="0" taxable="false" tradable="false"> <!-- used for monetarization, cannot be stolen, is not considered in ranking -->  
    <Name lang="de_DE">Kröte</Name>
    <Name lang="en_US">Golden Frog</Name>
    <Flavour lang="de_DE">Jeder mag Kröten! Die Steinzeitwährung.</Flavour>
    <Flavour lang="en_US">Everyone likes Golden Frogs - the currency of the Stone Age.</Flavour>
    <Description lang="de_DE">
      <p>Quasi-Währung in der Steinzeit. Gerne genommen bei jeglichem Tauschhandel.</p>
    </Description>
    <Description lang="en_US">
      <p>A type of Stone Age currency, readily accepted in any barter transaction.</p>
    </Description>
  </Resource>
</ResourceTypes>
